

#### Personal

Name Olha Shevel

Address 39 Dovzhenko Street 10002 Zhytomyr

Phone number +380636169291

#### **Email**

o.v.shevel@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/olhashevel-66a6b9166/

### Languages

EnglishC1RussianC1UkrainianNative

# Olha Shevel

A self-motivated and highly responsible student with 3 years of experience as a content manager. English knowledge at the advanced level, slight knowledge of web technologies and software engineering processes. Enthusiastic about passing new challenges and obtaining new experiences.

### Work experience

#### Content manager

Jun 2018 - Nov 2021

Spheremall, Zhytomyr

Responsibilities:

- · Content filling of websites
- Providing support and consultation on product exploitation
- · Optimizing SEO information

## **QA Engineer**

Nov 2021 - Present

Spheremall, Zhytomyr

Responsibilities:

- · Manual testing of websites
- · Automation test support
- · Creating automated tests using Java JUnit framework and Selenium utility
- · Configuring and monitoring tests in Jenkins

### **Education and Qualifications**

High School 2016 - 2020

Zhytomyr City Lyceum, Zhytomyr

Liberal arts education in English philology class

Bachelor 2020 - Present

The National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute", Kyiv Faculty of Informatics and Computer Science

## Skills

- Java
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Svelte
- MySQL

#### Licenses & certifications

First Certificate in English (Level C1) Issued Mar 2021